blackfilm.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Policy - Blackfilm - Black Movies, Television, and Theatre News

Your privacy is important to us.  Because we gather certain types of information about you when you visit our site, we want you to understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information.  This Privacy Policy (the Policy) describes the kind of information we gather about you, the way we use the information we collect, whether we disclose information about you to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of information about you.  This Policy is applicable to any current or future entity(ies) controlled by, controlling or under common control with blackfilm.com.

**1.  The Information We Collect**

Although we do not maintain records about the way that you, as an individual, navigate our web site or what you read on our site, we do gather general information about your usage of the site.  The information we collect about you is aggregated with information about other users.  For example, we track the number of visitors to our site and the number of visitors that view each page of the site, as well as the frequency of their visits and the search terms that they enter into the site’s search mechanism.  The aggregated information we collect helps us to identify your likes and dislikes with regard to the site and is analogous to network television ratings that report the number of people who tuned in to watch a program.  Like television ratings, blackfilm.com will only track and use such data as it relates to user activity as a whole, as opposed to you individually.

In order to join the blackfilm.com community you will be required to register with us.  During registration, you’ll be asked to provide us with certain information about yourself, such as your name, age, gender, zip code and other demographic information or information of general interest to blackfilm.com.  Some of the information on the registration form is mandatory, other sections of the form request information that you may provide solely at your discretion.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve the ads displayed on our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email or phone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see http://optout.networkadvertising.org.

**2.  How We Use the Information We Collect**

The information you share with us when you register may be used in several ways.  Typically, during your visit to blackfilm.com, we will use your registration information to verify that access to certain areas of the site (for example, the message board) is appropriate.  Demographic and other personal information you provide when you register is also used to enhance your blackfilm.com experience.  For example, we may use such information to prepare future content based upon the collective interests of our users, or to communicate with you about changes and improvements to blackfilm.com or about events we are hosting.  We also use your information to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.blackfilm.com/terms.htm#Terms%20and%20Conditions%20of%20Use) and/or this Policy.

The aggregated information that we collect about our users is disclosed to our promotional and business partners.  We do this to educate our partners about who you are so they can provide you with the best possible content and web experience.  From time to time, blackfilm.com, our affiliates, promotional, and/or business partners may communicate with you to call certain products, special offers, or unique content to your attention based upon the personal information you provide when you register.  If you would prefer not to receive direct communications from our promotional or business partners, you will be given an opportunity to decline when you register and again at any other time you are asked to provide us with information.

In addition, blackfilm.com will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: (i) we have your consent to share the information; (ii) we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested (in such event, unless we tell you differently, third-parties do not have any right to use your personal information beyond what is necessary to assist us); (iii) the purpose and manner of disclosure is clearly defined in advance; (iv) we respond to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process; (v) we believe in good faith that disclosure is legally required or to protect our rights; or (vi) we find that your actions on our web site violate our web site’s [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.blackfilm.com/terms.htm#Terms%20and%20Conditions%20of%20Use), or any of our usage guidelines.

**3.  Links**

Our web site contains links to other web sites.  Please note that when you click on one of these links you are being sent to another web site.  These sites may not follow the same privacy policies as blackfilm.com.  For example, they may send their own cookies to you, and as a result, collect data that blackfilm.com does not collect.  Therefore, we encourage you to read the privacy statements of these sites as their policies may differ from this Policy.

We do not use encryption to protect the data that you submit to our site.  Information that you submit travels through the Internet and, to the extent that such information is disclosed in public areas, it will become public information. Accordingly, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information to us, or through e-mails, or otherwise through the site.

Finally, you should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information on our message board or chat room, that information can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.  Such activities are beyond the control of blackfilm.com.

**4.  Children**

**BLACKFILM.COM IS A GENERAL INTEREST SITE NOT INTENDED FOR CHILDREN UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE.   THEREFORE, PERSONS UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE ARE NOT PERMITTED TO REGISTER FOR ANY BLACKFILM.COM SERVICE, EVENT, OR PROMOTIONAL OFFER.**

**5.  Your Ability to Edit & Delete Your Information & Preferences**

blackfilm.com gives you the ability to edit your blackfilm.com membership information and preferences at any time, including whether you want blackfilm.com, its affiliates or promotional partners to contact you about matters unrelated to the web site, this Policy or the [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.blackfilm.com/terms.htm#Terms%20and%20Conditions%20of%20Use).  You may change or update your registration information, or terminate your blackfilm.com membership, at any time by sending an e-mail to [info@blackfilm.com](mailto:info@blackfilm.com) with appropriate instructions.

**6.  Changes to this Policy**

blackfilm.com reserves the right to change this Policy at any time.  Please check this page periodically for changes to this Policy.  Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.  This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact:

**blackfilm.com  
375 Greenwich Street  
New York, NY 10013  
**

This Policy is an integral part of our [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.blackfilm.com/terms.htm#Terms%20and%20Conditions%20of%20Use), together this Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use constitute the entire agreement between you and blackfilm.com relating to the use and enjoyment of our web site and supersede any and all other agreements, representations and understandings, whether written or oral.
